Okay, in this clip we're going to be drawing hair on our queen, and what we'll do is we'll start kind of like right along the edges here, and she, her hair is going to be very interesting.
We're going to make it very, very full, and very poofy.
Back then, the the styles were that if you, the richer you were, and the more royal you were, the more detailing got put into your, your face and your hair, and you knew that that woman was definitely royal if she had a very high, high hairdo; had it all up.
None of it down here, nothing below the ears really, just all up.
I mean, if she wore her hair down, that was either a sign that she was like so lower class type peasant, or she was maybe a, you know, just younger; like a princess or something like that, but that once you reached a certain age, you were never caught dead with your hair down, and you can sort of have a little fun with her.
Like make her, at this point, look like she's got like a big old afro.
And then what we'll do is we're going to really have some fun here.
We're going to draw a huge, huge feather coming off the top of her head there; a big, big, big thing, and this will be sort of her little headdress.
So, just kind of start by drawing the lower edges of it; just lightly kind of come down; draw the, lightly, the edges.
Now come down like this; come up and draw a definite shape though.
As you can see, the huge feather coming out of her head.
I come down the sides like this; draw the stem, a clearly defined stem coming up, and that will be the top portion of our good queen's hair.
Now what you want to do also, is make sure there's a clear line defining where the feather begins, and where the hair ends, cause' you don't want people confusing the two.
You want people to clearly see that that is a feather on top of our good queen's head.
Don't draw too much detail in there, because you don't want to, you know, you don't want to call too much attention to it, even though it is like hard to ignore really.
It is sticking out of her head, after all.
But yeah, I'd say we have a good start here, and what we'll do now is we'll move on to the next portion, and draw her shoulders.
So, if you got the hair and the feather all set, go ahead and move onto....